(EP08 Behind-the-Scenes)
(Behind-the-Scenes 1)
(Heart-Thumping Couple Ranking:
Special Surprise)
There are blue flowers here.
So many colors.
Do you remember this place?
Of course.
We had our first date here.
Yes.
We'll make these
(Materials for kites)
little kites
and plant dyes.
(Botanical dyeing)
We'll unlock them through some games.
(SiYi couple Pictionary)
(Draw a question for each round.)
(Draw your answer at the same time.)
(If you fail
to guess your partner's answer,)
(you'll be punished.)
(Complete the game
to unlock two pairs of kites.)
Where's the question card?
Right here.
(Flips to look)
Why are you peeking?
You do it.
You go first.
(Question)
The best food you've eaten recently.
(Glances)
I have one in mind.
I had it yesterday.
And the day before.
Really?
Three days ago too.
(Giving the answer through eye contact)
(Got it)
Sure. Let's start.
(Glances)
Why did you pick this color too?
(Both pick pink)
Could we be drawing
Could we...
the same thing?
Woah.
(Glances)
It makes my hand look so dark.
(Can't hold it in)
(Demonstrating)
Really. I've been staring at my hand.
I can't take it anymore.
It's the same tone as my jacket.
(Makes skin look dark)
(Can't stop laughing)
The kite is white.
Makes the tan stand out.
You're not tan.
(Stares)
I'm done.
Me too.
Alright.
Can you guess
what I drew?
That's a bubble tea.
(Bubble tea)
This is mutton.
(Mutton)
Yes.
(Milk skin)
This is milk skin.
(Got all correct)
Yes.
(Bubble tea, milk skin, mutton)
So smart.
(Praises)
What you drew
is also the milk skin.
(Milk skin)
Biscuit.
(Biscuit)
And this is the milk cube.
(Milk cube)
This is a yogurt cube.
(Yogurt cube)
This is bubble tea.
(Bubble tea)
And this is a cheese stick.
(Cheese stick)
You got it right.
(Got it all right. Milk skin, biscuit,
cheese, milk cube, milk tea, yogurt cube)
(Challenge successful)
Telepathy.
Let's see who gets
to draw this perfect kite.
A masterpiece by Baoding Van Gogh.
I'm not.
Next one then.
Next one.
Draw a card.
(Question)
Your favorite thing to do in the house.
Let's start.
(Blocks view)
You can't look at mine.
I won't.
(Defending)
(Sneaks a peek)
(Catches him)
(Covers)
Don't peek at mine.
(Defending)
How am I supposed to block you?
(Trying not to laugh)
I'm done.
Me too.
Let me guess.
Playing badminton?
No.
Cooking?
What is it?
(Trying again)
Go for a drive?
No.
Chatting?
Dreaming?
Dreaming.
Did you have too much to drink?
No.
(Joking around)
(Sneaks a peek)
(Laughs)
Eating breakfast.
You saw something, didn't you?
(Denying)
I didn't.
Yours is about breakfast.
No.
Just eating then.
Yes.
(Wu Siying's answer: Eating)
I said it earlier.
You said no.
You guessed cooking.
I did.
But not eating.
Cooking.
Fine. You won't get this right.
Give it a go.
Stargazing room.
Go on a date.
Go for a walk.
Did I get any of it right?
(Anticipates)
No.
I...
(Yihang's answer: Making eye contact)
Because I drew us having eye contact.
You got it all wrong.
What do we do?
Accept the punishment together.
For the punishment,
(Punishment)
name one of your partner's flaws or quirks.
Once I say it,
you have to admit it's true.
You go first.
I think
you're a little too blunt sometimes.
A little too blunt?
Do you agree?
Yes. I admit it.
(Instantly agrees)
It's my turn now.
You take forever in the bathroom.
(Warning look)
(Pinches)
I didn't say anything.
(Backs down)
(Starting over)
But you guessed it wrong too.
You have to name a flaw or little quirk.
(Restarts)
Your flaw is that you're too skinny.
(Oh)
I don't agree.
(Third attempt)
Didn't you guess it wrong?
No. I'm thinking.
You have to name a flaw or little quirk.
(Restarts)
(Glances)
(Finally gets it)
A little quirk.
You like to pretend to be a zombie.
Pretend to be a zombie.
(Subtitles have left the chat)
(Agrees)
Sure.
Alright. We're done with this.
Let's do the botanical dye.
Let's make up a new rule.
(Winner gets to choose a plant dye first)
Rock goes like this.
(Shy)
What's rock?
(Asking on purpose)
Rock.
This is rock.
This is scissors.
This is paper.
(Does it again)
(Amused)
Did you get it?
No.
(Teasing)
This is rock.
This is scissors.
This is paper.
Teach me again.
Rock.
(Copies him)
Scissors.
Paper.
Okay.
Alright.
Let's start.
(Starting)
Rock.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Scissors, rock)
I won.
I want green.
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Scissors)
(Rock, scissors)
I won.
You get to pick now.
I want the blue one.
The blue? Sure.
One last round.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Scissors, paper)
- I lost.
- I won.
I want this one.
Sure.
What do you want to make?
Something beautiful.
Beautiful.
Everyone will like it.
I'm sure they will.
(Leans in for a closer look)
Do you know what this is?
What's this?
These are fallen leaves.
I thought it was
crispy sweet-and-sour pork.
They're fallen leaves.
Fall's almost here.
Mine is really cool.
Super cool.
Look at what I made.
Guess what it is.
(Cui Yihang's work)
Can you guess it?
This is the roasted mutton leg
you had yesterday.
What mutton leg?
What is it then?
A swing.
Swing?
(Leaves and swing)
These are leaves and a swing.
You should stamp two little figures
on it.
Two figures?
Great idea.
I'll redo this one.
(Continues to work on it)
Here.
Careful with your hand.
These two figures.
(Swing)
Alright. Let's make one together.
I'm hitting you.
You are?
I'll hit you then.
I need to hit it harder.
Done.
(Rowing)
I have a game suggestion.
What game?
A few days ago, didn't we play
(Suggests playing Tour the Three Gardens)
Tour the Three Gardens?
The loser draws one of these.
(Loser draws a punishment slip)
There's a punishment inside.
Sure.
(SiYi couple Tour the Three Gardens)
(Pick a garden.)
(Take turns naming things
in the garden.)
(No repeats or hesitations.)
(The loser has to draw
a dialect challenge.)
(Complete the challenge
to unlock 13 pairs of botanical dyes.)
There are so many flowers.
Let's tour the garden.
The garden?
Sure.
Hmm.
Alright.
(Round One officially begins)
(Laughs along)
For real.
(Starting over)
Let's...
What?
What were you going to say?
How do you want to say it?
I'll say,
"Let's tour the garden together."
Then I'll say, "What's in the garden?"
Let's tour the garden together.
What's in the garden?
I'll go first.
Yes.
There are roses in the garden.
Chrysanthemums.
Little chrysanthemums.
Begonias.
Peonies.
Peonies?
Draw a punishment.
(Cui Yihang has to take a punishment
in Round One)
(Say, "OMG, you're so freaking cute!"
in the Northeastern dialect)
It's a Northeastern dialect challenge.
Say it in the Northeastern accent.
I can't.
Teach me.
Let me hear you try.
"OMG, you're so freaking cute."
Is that right?
Who's freaking cute?
(Teasing)
You are.
Did you say so?
How about this?
"OMG,"
"Si is so freaking cute."
(Si is so freaking cute)
Si is so freaking cute.
How was that?
Pretty cute.
Let's have another round.
Where do you want to tour?
The vegetable garden.
Vegetable garden?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's tour the vegetable garden.
What's in the vegetable garden?
There are eggplants.
Rapeseed.
Corn.
Potatoes.
I said it.
(You didn't)
You said eggplant.
I said potatoes.
Potatoes were the first thing I said.
(You really didn't)
You said eggplant.
I'll let you have this one.
Fine.
You're letting me have it?
(Game continues)
Potatoes.
Tomatoes.
Green beans.
Cucumbers.
(Fails again)
Here.
(Cui Yihang has to take a punishment
in Round Two)
(Say, "Bang bang, two punches
out of nowhere.")
(in the Northeastern dialect)
Bang bang, two punches out of nowhere.
Do you know why
it doesn't sound convincing?
Say it again.
Bang bang...
You need to add some action.
I need to make it hurt.
Let's keep drawing?
Okay.
Great.
I hope they're happy
when they receive it.
They'll be happy for a whole month
when they get it.
A whole lifetime.
That amazing?
This is everyone's love for us.
We've received it.
Love in every color.
Pass it on.
You're really earned
that Baoding Van Gogh title.
Pretty good, huh?
Yes. It's very vivid.
So impressive.
A four-leaf clover
is a symbol of good luck.
I hope everyone
can have a little more luck.
What do you think?
It's a great idea.
You're such a creative girl
with so many ideas.
I'm done.
Where is this?
(Answers instantly)
Confession night.
Which one?
The mid-show confession.
Because you were wearing black.
This is the flower.
What color was it?
This is the phone.
(By the sea, Si)
Write them some wishes.
(Writing wishes for everyone)
Let's take some polaroids to give them.
Let's pack them up.
Sure.
(Starts packing)
We should wrap this up.
We hope those who got our presents
can stay happy every day.
Bye bye.
=Heart Signal (China Version) S9=
(SVIP updates every Mon & Tue at noon)
(VIP updates every Tue & Wed at noon,
one week early)
(Behind-the-Scenes 2)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
This is awesome.
Woah.
Welcome, everyone, to our home.
You can hear the sea.
The sea's right there!
I want to run over.
This is great.
Will you swim?
Will people swim here?
Will people swim?
I'll swim now. Let's go!
Don't scare me.
Let me feel it.
My gosh.
This feels so great.
This is amazing.
I feel like all my fatigue
has been wiped away.
It's gone.
Totally wiped away.
I could just lie down here.
A once-in-a-lifetime trip.
Cherish it.
Cherish all of this.
All of it.
(Behind-the-Scenes 3)
(Behind-the-Scenes: Couples House)
Have you not made
a presentation in a while?
Yeah.
I graduated. Why would I make one?
Let me show you
my presentation masterclass.
I'm really good at making them.
(Serious)
Are you thinking
about how you want to present it?
I'll just prepare a script
and read it.
Ten minutes for presentation
and another ten for Q&A.
Are you nervous?
Not really?
A little.
I keep thinking
you're waiting for me here.
So I need to finish quickly.
Finish it properly
then hurry back.
Hopefully it'll go smoothly.
It will.
(Glances)
You need to go out tomorrow.
You promised you'd enjoy
the scenery for me.
It's so beautiful here.
I think Beijing is pretty beautiful too.
You can see Beijing every day.
I'll take you around every day later.
But only if you're there.
I know.
I was just worried you'd get too tired.
I won't.
(Behind-the-Scenes 4)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Hi.
You're back.
It's just...
(Motions)
Where are you going?
Outside.
What's wrong?
I'm going out.
What?
This is
for you.
My gosh.
And it happens to be blue and black.
Thank you.
You had a blue
and black one too yesterday.
Thank you. It's pretty.
(Takes it)
I got this because...
I think it really
suits your style.
What's this?
It's actually a pair of sunglasses.
And I thought the new packaging
looks really cool.
I want to see what's inside.
It looks like this.
Look at it when you get back.
So yeah.
Thank you.
My lord.
It's nice.
(Behind-the-Scenes 5)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Do you want to try the seafood fried rice?
Pass it around.
This is delicious.
Thank you.
Thanks.
(Glances)
I'll hold it down for you.
(Helps)
Here.
Okay. Thank you.
What's this?
Scallop. Do you want one?
I'll have one spring roll.
The scallop, right?
(Serving each other)
Have this.
What's this?
It's...
The one just now.
I think I had some.
Do you like it?
It's pretty good.
Cut it up.
Did you try the sticky rice?
The sticky rice?
Yeah. I thought it was pretty good.
Thanks.
(Glances)
Where should I put this? Here?
Yeah, I'll put it on the spoon.
Beef.
I'll grab some beef.
I'll try a small piece.
Okay.
There's a cat.
Can they eat shrimp and stuff?
It can eat this fish.
What a good kitty.
It's acting all shy.
It looks like a little leopard.
(Behind-the-Scenes 6)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Sha Yue'er, sit.
Sit.
Woah.
There's a plate of meat here.
Tell me if you can't reach them.
I will.
I'll get some for you.
Sha Yue'er, get me some fish.
Sure.
A little more.
I'll share it with Cao Yiheng.
(Serves*1)
(Serves*2)
(Serves*3)
Do you eat mushrooms?
Yes.
(Serves*N)
Did you try the sticky rice?
No.
That's so good. You haven't tried it?
Which one?
I'll steal some rice.
Steal some rice.
A buffet.
A whole plateful.
For you.
Thanks.
Thank you, Sha Yue'er.
So much.
It's delicious.
(Behind-the-Scenes 7)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
It looks like a heart.
Yeah. Take a picture of it.
We must.
Cui Kaiyi,
we'd like your help.
Not a problem.
(Look up)
We'll take a picture of you two.
What's wrong?
Look. A heart!
It is.
Like that.
An abstract one.
Let's take a photo from behind.
I'll take a polaroid for you.
Sure. Can we include the heart?
Okay.
Honestly,
the wind is making my eyes water.
Are you tearing up?
Yes.
Three, two, one.
The photo is going to be amazing.
I can't keep my eyes open.
Are we facing the light?
Or is it backlighting.
How should I take it for you both?
We want to stand here.
Stand there.
Either works.
Or over there?
Let's do it over there.
We'll take one here. Thank you.
Ready.
Wait.
Let me fix my hair.
(Helps fix her hair)
Ready.
Three, two, one.
Thank you.
Perfect.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
(Behind-the-Scenes 8)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Anything you want to try?
I'm very scared of the flying one.
If two people can do it together...
You and me.
Would you be scared?
Would it make you feel better?
I'm afraid of heights.
Okay.
It doesn't go that high,
and it's really steady.
It's not like you'll suddenly drop.
You just stay up there, nice and steady.
What kind is it?
Paragliding?
Not paragliding.
A boat pulls you along,
and the parachute slowly lifts you up.
It's not scary.
You should try it.
What do you think?
Give it a try.
I'll see.
Are you still feeling sick?
Feeling any better?
If you don't feel well...
I'll just close my eyes for a bit.
Don't worry.
No, I mean, if you're
still sleepy later,
you can lie down
on the lounge chair
after we get ashore.
Get some rest.
Okay.
(Behind-the-Scenes 9)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Hello.
Hello..
What're you up to?
Writing my thesis.
I have a thesis defense tomorrow.
Thesis defense?
Where?
Back in Beijing.
Tomorrow?
I'll be going for two days.
I'll be back on the 18th.
I'm leaving Cao Yiheng in your care.
Babysit him.
This is so sudden.
Yeah. Way too sudden.
When are you coming back?
The 18th.
I'll be here in the morning.
It's only two days. He's in your care.
Stay safe.
You'll do great.
I will.
Good luck.
Good luck!
I'll leave him in your care.
We'll keep an eye on him.
He's been sad all day.
Separation anxiety again, huh?
Nothing I can do.
(Behind-the-Scenes 10)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
How much older are your sisters?
One is three years older,
and one is seven years older.
Any generation gap between you all?
Nope.
That's nice.
You have family around.
Yeah.
Do you usually go to the movies alone?
Rarely.
What kind do you like?
Comedy, romance, or family drama?
Comedy.
And also
Hong Kong, China movies.
You don't really watch family
or romance movies, do you?
Yeah.
Lesser compared to the others.
You mostly watch romance movies.
No. I rarely watch them.
If we are watching one together,
would you be fine
with watching anything?
Yeah.
Anything is fine.
(Thinking)
How much do you still hold back?
(Asks)
I don't think I hold back much
when it's just the two of us.
When we're with everyone else,
I always feel like...
Should be more polite.
More proper.
What does that mean?
Nothing.
Are you like that too?
Of course.
Not so much now.
I feel like you can do
whatever you want.
Don't overthink it.
We're pretty comfortable
with everyone now.
Yeah.
(Behind-the-Scenes 11)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Yu Xiaoyang
Yes.
Who am I?
You are...
(Thinking)
Liang Xiaofang.
Liang Xiaofang?
- That works too.
- Liang Xiaofang.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
You stepped on my toe.
Let me see.
It feels fine.
Really?
I didn't feel any pain
when you stepped on it.
Let's sit for a bit.
Okay.
Take a seat.
Here.
It's so hot.
I want to take off my glasses.
How do I look? This spot.
(Leans in)
Don't move.
There are two marks here.
Can you close your eyes?
Let me check my reflection.
Okay. You can open them now.
How could you be this pretty?
(Behind-the-Scenes 12)
(Behind-the-Scenes: Heart Signal)
Do you think love
is purely emotional
with no rationality involved at all?
I think at the beginning,
your feelings for someone
are purely emotional,
because you can't bring logic into it.
So in the early stages,
I focus on trying to get to know you.
So
you take it one step at a time.
Yes. In the beginning.
Because you need to know
if they even want to get to know you.
By the middle stages, I realize
that you're someone who overthinks
and gets scared easily.
Once I have
a basic understanding of you,
I'd feel that given your personality,
those actions were actually
positive signs to me.
You'd be thinking
how you can build
on those positive signals,
or how we can get
to know each other better.
And I'd also be willing
to make some compromises.
I get it, bro.
Alright, sis.
(Behind-the-Scenes 13)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
We can call each other every night.
Don't be sad.
I'm not.
Hugs.
Don't be upset, okay?
I'm not upset.
Good boy.
I want to stay with you too.
I've gotten so used to having you
by my side these past few days.
(Lock gazes)
It's only for two days.
I'll be right back.
I'll fly there
and fly right back.
But if you miss me
or are worried about me,
just tell me.
I'll call you right away.
(Moves closer)
Okay.
Yeah.
I'll call you at night.
In the future too.
Call me anytime when you miss me.
I will.
That's just how I am.
That's great. Me too.
Call me anytime.
Okay.
(Behind-the-Scenes 14)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Hello.
There's food too.
There is.
Do you want to eat?
I'm fine. Depends if you want some.
So you kind of do.
Let's see what looks good.
I wonder if they have ice cream.
There's this coconut.
Yeah. This too.
Let's see what they order.
Go forward.
See what you want to eat.
(Blocks)
I'm confiscating this.
Let's go.
Let's go over there.
Over there? Okay.
Look at the menu.
Decide what you want.
What do you want to eat?
This one.
Okay. One fried banana with ice cream.
I want this one.
One fried chicken.
Yes.
Pick one more.
The one you picked.
Sure. We'll have one of those.
Coconut sago.
Okay.
How do I pay?
Wait.
Let me.
I scanned the QR.
I scanned it.
(Blocks)
I really did. It's done.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
(Same old rule)
No.
Okay.
Thank you. Let's go.
(Behind-the-Scenes 15)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Let's see what we can do.
Arm wrestling.
Let's do it.
You're drinking mine, aren't you?
I don't know.
That's definitely not yours.
I grabbed the wrong one.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'll wipe it.
I'll make it up to you.
How about this?
Chen Hewen, use all your strength,
and she'll use both hands.
Okay. Let's try it.
Three, two, one.
Come on!
Move your hand over here.
Come on.
Put some muscle into it.
But Sha Yue'er has some muscle
in her forearms.
Look at her forearms.
I have muscles in my upper arms too.
Mr. Chen, you won.
Mr. Chen is now
the reigning champion.
Liang Xiaoyu, do you want to challenge him?
Liang Xiaoyu, try it.
I don't want to challenge him.
How about you two do it?
Let's do it.
Right hand first.
Move over here.
Let me watch them.
This should be fun.
Watch them play.
This is worth watching.
So fun to watch.
Come on.
This is worth watching.
Three, two, one.
Well.
Let's use the left hand.
Try the left.
So quick.
Left hand. Three, two, one.
Does anyone want to make a prediction?
My left hand is too weak.
This is the difference
between lefties and righties.
(Behind-the-Scenes 16)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
(Behind-the-Scenes 17)
("Weekend Crush" early access preview)
It's our anniversary.
Yes. One month.
You start drawing.
I'll just go grab something.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Go ahead.
What is he doing?
How are you? Any better?
What have you drawn?
How is it?
I think yours looks better than mine.
Stargazing room.
Yes.
It really looks like it.
The hot pot we missed that day.
Yes.
Delicious.
A very unique stargazing room.
There's a star.
So pretty.
It looks better than that one.
Does it look good?
Yes.
(Picking Cui Kaiyi up for school)
Let's report to the school.
So what's my role?
Just hold the umbrella steady.
The princess' study buddy.
My student card.
Got everything?
Yup.
Let me see your card.
(Shows card)
We're going to get some food.
Capital Medical University welcomes you.
Bye bye.
=Heart Signal (China Version) S9=
(SVIP updates every Mon & Tue at noon)
(VIP episodes update every Tues at noon,
members get one-week early access.)